coasterfurniture.com 2018-05-09

# Privacy Policy - Coaster Fine Furniture - Furniture Store

Coaster Fine Furniture is a furniture retailer in . The Company's mission is to create an efficient, informative, and enjoyable online shopping environment that enables our consumers to:

  * Access the largest selection of furniture available in one place
  * Find all the information necessary to make educated purchasing decisions
  * Conveniently search for furniture in a manner tailored to the way in which each customer wishes to shop
  * Receive premier customer service in a personal, supportive environment
  * Satisfy all furniture needs in a one-stop shopping environment

Coaster Fine Furniture offers a much greater selection of furniture than could be cost effectively shown in a physical showroom. The Coaster Fine Furniture web site is designed to be the ultimate self-service shopping environment with powerful search tools, rich product information, and educational editorial content. We are committed to providing our customers with the highest levels of service. As such our web site is supported by a telephone and web-based call center, which is staffed with knowledgeable and helpful sales associates. Shopping for furniture can be difficult and frustrating. Coaster Fine Furniture is committed to creating an online marketplace where you can find a huge selection of products at competitively low prices.

## Information this Site Gathers & Tracks

The Coaster Fine Furniture web site logs cookies, IP addresses and browser types, but we do not link this information to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user’s session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous.

You can browse our site without entering any personal information and therefore remain anonymous during your visit. However, we hope that all of our visitors will register with us so that we can learn more about our valuable customers and keep them updated with our newsletter and provide personalized service. Our registration form and feedback form asks users for some or all of the following information: connotation, name, company, title, email address, phone number, username, password, preferences, comments, and various types of demographic information. The username, email address, and password are often used to uniquely identify an individual so that that individual may access particular online resources such as their saved shopping cart, profile information, and order status. This information may also be used to modify the web site in order to enhance your shopping experience. We use this information to process your orders, to keep you updated on your orders and to personalize your shopping experience. Our secure servers protect the information using advanced encryption and firewall technology. Your personal information cannot be read as it travels to our ordering system. In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by reputable third-party banking, distribution institutions and manufacturers. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card and to process your order. They are under strict obligation to keep your personal information private. They use this data to process the order and we provide only the information required to complete the transaction. Our partners are not permitted to sell, rent or share this information.

At this time, Coaster Fine Furniture will not take your credit card number online. Upon receipt of your order inquiry, a member of our customer service department will contact you to complete your transaction and schedule a delivery.

Coaster Fine Furniture does not give, sell, rent or trade prospect information to third parties. The information you must provide for a purchase includes: Your billing information: first name, last name, title, company, email address, phone number, coupon code and additional comments. Items in bold are required pieces of information.

Exception: If you arrived at the Coaster Fine Furniture web site from one of our Partner sites participating in a Co-Branded site (indicated by both the Coaster Fine Furniture logo and the Partner's logo displayed on the top of the page) then information about your purchase may, in some cases, be distributed back to the Partner site.

## Use of the Information this Site Gathers & Tracks

The Coaster Fine Furniture web site logs IP addresses for systems administration purposes and these logs will be analyzed to constantly improve the value of the materials available on the web site.

## Coaster Fine Furniture Registration Form

We encourage all visitors to register with Coaster Fine Furniture. Your name and email address are used to send you our newsletter containing product updates and special offers. If you would rather not receive the newsletter, but would still like to register, please indicate your preference by marking the appropriate box presented on the registration form. Occasionally, we like to present you with special offers from our partners. This involves sharing your information with them so they can send you the offer. If you prefer, you can choose that your information not be shared with our partners by indicating your preference on the registration form. Preferences and demographic information is used to help us improve our service and products. The more we know about you, the better we can serve you.

## Coaster Fine Furniture Order Form

At this time, Coaster Fine Furniture does not accept or process orders on this website, and will not take your credit card number online. In the future, we plan to incorporate secure, online transactions. When this change is made we will update this privacy policy.

## Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks

For those visitors who register with Coaster Fine Furniture, we may share your preferences and demographic information with select partners, but will never sell or rent your personally identifiable information to any third party without your consent. Please see the Opt-out section below.

The information that you submit on the order form (contact and billing information) is never shared with any third parties, including our partners (excluding partners participating in a Co-Branded site...see "Exception below").

Exception: If you arrived at the Coaster Fine Furniture web site from one of our Partner sites participating in a Co-Branded site (indicated by both the Coaster Fine Furniture logo and the Partner's logo displayed on the top of the page) then information about your purchase may, in some cases, be distributed back to the Partner site.

## Accessing/Reviewing/Updating Your Customer Record Information

The ability for a customer to modify his/her information on the Coaster Fine Furniture web site and track an order is currently not available. We plan to make this functionality available in the future. The privacy policy will be updated when such changes are made. As a customer, you may contact Coaster Fine Furniture directly via phone or email to request to view or make any changes to your personal info. If you would like to view, correct and/or update your registration information, please contact us.

## Security

At this time, Coaster Fine Furniture will not take your credit card number online. Upon receipt of your order inquiry, a member of our customer service department will prepare a customized freight quote that is best handled on a case-by-case basis at this time. The shipping companies Coaster Fine Furniture has contracted base freight charges on a number of variables and are not standardized at this time. After you have reviewed the quote, the customer service representative will take your credit card number over the phone and process your order. If you do not want to pay by credit card, you can send Coaster Fine Furniture a money order or treasurer's check.

## Links

The Coaster Fine Furniture web site may contain links to other web sites. Please be aware that our privacy policy does not apply to these linked sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any web site.

## Cookies

Our site uses cookies so that we may keep track of items in your shopping cart and to provide our visitors with a tailored user experience. With the help of cookies, we can present you with customized content and ads that will be of more interest to you. We also use cookies to remember your passwords for you so you don’t have to re-enter them each time you visit the site. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies. However, if certain cookies that track your purchase are rejected then we won't be able to keep items in your cart.

## Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our web site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our web site is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## Opt-out Policy

If at any time after registering, you change your mind about receiving the newsletter or sharing your information with third parties, you may Contact Us.

## How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact:

Coaster Fine Furniture  
Click here to contact us online

Nothing on this page may be copied or reproduced without explicit permission.
